Welcome to the unit.
Learning to learn. B.
Millie and her classmates are talking about the most important thing for successful learning.
Work in groups and give your opinions.
Use the conversation below as a model.
Do you think it's important for successful learning, Daniel?
For me, one thing is to have strong drive to learn.
If you're willing to learn, you'll work harder.
Yes, I agree.
And it's also important to have a good teacher.
A good teacher will guide you on the right path. True.
And you need to have good study skills.
They'll help you learn better. That's right.
And we should also make a study plan.
It'll help us manage our time well.
I couldn't agree more.